oklivetv.com 2017-06-27

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which OK Live TV collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the “www.oklivetv.com” website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all services offered by OKLiveTV.com

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

OK Live TV may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _– To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _– To improve our Site_  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Content**

**We DO NOT host any broadcasts on this website/server.** All streams found on our site are found freely available around the web on sites such as Justin.tv, Ustream.tv, VShare, etc. We make no guarantees or promises in our service and take no liability for our users actions. We are not affiliated neither claim to be affiliated with any of the owners of broadcasts/streams played on our site.  
Whereas we do not filter such references, we cannot and do not attempt to control, censor, or block any material that may be considered offensive, defamatory, libelous, obnoxious, inaccurate, deceptive, unlawful or otherwise distressing neither do we accept responsibility for such content or the consequences of such content being made available.  
Material may be inappropriately described or subject to restrictions such as copyright, licensing and other limitations, and it is the responsibility of those having access to such material to comply with any and all lawful obligations arising from such material coming into their possession and thus mitigate any alleged transgression.  
Therefore, regarding access to content:  
All users warrant that they are 18 years of age or older, and therefore qualified to enter into this Agreement either as an individual or as a corporate entity.  
All users undertake to comply with the national laws applicable to the country in which they reside and observe the rights inherent in any copyright material whilst upholding the rights of any copyright owner.  
All users are advised to use caution, exercise discretion and use common sense and personal judgment when using this site or any references detailed within, and to respect the wishes of others who may value freedom from censorship as consenting adults equal to (or possibly superior to) your own personal preferences.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

OK Live TV has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
